Guide to the Newspaper Guild of New York Records WAG.125
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Early Records: Shop Files, 1935-1950
  - Jewish Morning Journal: Negotiations, 1946-1947 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Jewish Morning Journal: Grievances, 1947-1950 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Jewish Telegraphic Agency: Minutes, 1947-1948 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Jewish Telegraphic Agency: Minutes, 1949 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Jewish Telegraphic Agency: Minutes, 1950 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Jewish Telegraphic Agency: Correspondence, 1945 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Jewish Telegraphic Agency: Correspondence, 1946-1948 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Jewish Telegraphic Agency: Negotiations, 1940-1941 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Jewish Telegraphic Agency: Negotiations, 1945-1946 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Jewish Telegraphic Agency: Negotiations, 1947 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Jewish Telegraphic Agency: Negotiations, 1947-1949 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Jewish Telegraphic Agency: Grievances, 1947-1950 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Jewish Telegraphic Agency: Contracts, 1947 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Journal American: Minutes, 1939-1950 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Journal American: Correspondence, 1940 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Journal American: Correspondence, 1943 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Journal American: Correspondence, 1944 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Journal American: Correspondence, 1945 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Journal American: Correspondence, 1946 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Journal American: Correspondence, 1947 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Journal American: Correspondence, 1948 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Journal American: Correspondence, 1948-1949 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Journal American: Correspondence, 1950 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Journal American: Negotiations, 1939 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Journal American: Negotiations, 1940 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Journal American: Negotiations I, 1940-1941 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Journal American: Negotiations II, 1940-1941 (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Journal American: Negotiations III, 1940-1941 (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Journal American: Negotiations IV, 1940-1941 (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Journal American: Negotiations, 1942 (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Journal American: Negotiations, 1943 (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Journal American: Negotiations, 1944 (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Journal American: Negotiations, 1944 (Box 42, Folder 36)
  - Journal American: Negotiations, 1945 (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - Journal American: Negotiations I, 1945-1946 (Box 42, Folder 38)
  - Journal American: Negotiations II, 1945-1946 (Box 42, Folder 39)
  - Journal American: Negotiations, 1947 (Box 42, Folder 40)
  - Journal American: Negotiations I, 1948 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Journal American: Negotiations II, 1948 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Journal American: Negotiations, 1948 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Journal American: Negotiations, 1949 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Journal American: Negotiations I, 1950 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Journal American: Negotiations II, 1950 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Journal American: Grievances I, 1939-1940 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Journal American: Grievances II, 1939-1940 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Journal American: Grievances III, 1939-1940 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Journal American: Grievances, 1939 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Journal American: Grievances, 1939 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Journal American: Grievances I, 1941 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Journal American: Grievances II, 1941 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Journal American: Grievances III, 1941 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Journal American: Grievances, 1944 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Journal American: Grievances, 1946 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Journal American: Grievances, 1946 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Journal American: Grievances, 1947 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Journal American: Grievances (McCarthy), 1949 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Journal American: Grievances, 1951 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Journal American: Shop Papers/Leaflets, 1939-1950 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Journal American: Contracts, 1939-1950 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Journal American: Clippings, 1941 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Journal of Commerce: Correspondence, 1946 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Journal of Commerce: Correspondence, 1946-1947 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Journal of Commerce: Correspondence, 1947 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Journal of Commerce: Correspondence, 1947 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Journal of Commerce: Correspondence, 1946-1948 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Journal of Commerce: Grievances, 1939 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - King Features: Correspondence, 1939-1940 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - King Features: Correspondence, 1940 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - King Features: Correspondence, 1940-1941 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - King Features: Correspondence (Calcagno), 1940-1941 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - King Features: Correspondence, 1941 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - King Features: Correspondence, 1942 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - King Features: Correspondence, 1945 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - King Features: Negotiations, 1940-1941 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - King Features: Grievances, 1940-1941 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - King Features: Shop Papers, undated (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - King Features: Contracts, 1938-1950 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Labor Press: Minutes, 1935-1950 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Labor Press: Correspondence, 1935-1941 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Labor Press: Correspondence, 1943 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Labor Press: Correspondence, 1944 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Labor Press: Correspondence, 1944 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Labor Press: Correspondence, 1945 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Labor Press: Correspondence, 1949-1950 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Labor Press: Negotiations, 1939-1940 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Labor Press: Negotiations, 1944-1945 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Labor Press: Negotiations, 1943-1945 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Labor Press: Negotiations, 1943-1945 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Labor Press: Negotiations, 1944 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Labor Press: Negotiations, 1945 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Labor Press: Grievances, 1945 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Labor Press: Grievances, 1950 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Labor Press: Contracts, 1935-1950 (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Long Island Press: Correspondence (Elections), 1939 (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - Long Island Press: Correspondence, 1940-1941 (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - Long Island Press: Correspondence, 1941 (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - Long Island Press: Correspondence, 1940-1941 (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - Long Island Press: Correspondence, 1941 (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - Long Island Press: Correspondence, 1945 (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - Long Island Press: Correspondence, 1944-1945 (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - Long Island Press: Correspondence, 1945 (Box 44, Folder 35)
  - Long Island Press: Correspondence, 1946 (Box 44, Folder 36)
  - Long Island Press: Correspondence, 1946 (Box 44, Folder 37)
  - Long Island Press: Correspondence, 1947 (Box 44, Folder 38)
  - Long Island Press: Correspondence, 1949 (Box 44, Folder 39)
  - Long Island Press: Correspondence, 1950 (Box 44, Folder 40)
  - Long Island Press: Negotiations, 1939-1940 (Box 44, Folder 41)
  - Long Island Press: Negotiations, 1941 (Box 44, Folder 42)
  - Long Island Press: Negotiations, 1941 (Box 44, Folder 43)
  - Long Island Press: Negotiations, 1942-1943 (Box 44, Folder 44)
  - Long Island Press: Negotiations, 1943-1944 (Box 44, Folder 45)
  - Long Island Press: Negotiations, 1945 (Box 44, Folder 46)
  - Long Island Press: Negotiations, 1945-1948 (Box 44, Folder 47)
  - Long Island Press: Negotiations, 1947 (Box 44, Folder 48)
  - Long Island Press: Negotiations, 1947-1948 (Box 44, Folder 49)
  - Long Island Press: Negotiations, 1948 (Box 44, Folder 50)
  - Long Island Press: Grievances, 1944 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Long Island Press: Grievances, 1943-1945 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Long Island Press: Grievances, 1945-1946 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Long Island Press: Grievances, 1946 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Long Island Press: Grievances, 1948-1949 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Long Island Press: Grievances I, 1939 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Long Island Press: Grievances II, 1939 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Long Island Press: Shop Papers, 1948-1950 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Long Island Press: Contracts, 1939-1950 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Look: Correspondence, 1941-1942 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Look: Correspondence, 1946 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Look: Correspondence, 1946 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Look: Correspondence, 1948 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Look: Correspondence, 1950 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Look: Correspondence, 1950 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Look: Negotiations, 1943 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Look: Negotiations, 1944 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Look: Negotiations, 1944 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Look: Negotiations, 1944 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Look: Negotiations, 1945 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Look: Negotiations, 1946 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Look: Negotiations, 1947 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Look: Negotiations, 1948 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Look: Negotiations, 1948 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Look: Negotiations, 1948 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Look: Negotiations, 1948 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Look: Negotiations, 1948 (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Look: Negotiations, 1949 (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Look: Negotiations, 1950 (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - Look: Negotiations, 1950 (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - Look: Grievances, 1948 (Box 45, Folder 31)
  - Look: Grievances, 1950 (Box 45, Folder 32)
  - Look: Contracts, 1946-1950 (Box 45, Folder 33)
  - Look: Clippings, 1935-1950 (Box 45, Folder 34)
  - Look: Shop Papers, 1943-1950 (Box 45, Folder 35)
  - Mirror: Correspondence, 1939-1941 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Mirror: Correspondence, 1940-1941 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Mirror: Correspondence, 1940-1941 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Mirror: Correspondence, 1939-1941 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Mirror: Correspondence, 1940-1941 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Mirror: Correspondence I, 1941 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Mirror: Correspondence II, 1941 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Mirror: Correspondence, 1943-1946 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Mirror: Correspondence, 1946 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Mirror: Correspondence, 1947 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Mirror: Correspondence, 1947 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Mirror: Correspondence, 1948-1949 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Mirror: Correspondence, 1948 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Mirror: Correspondence, 1950 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Mirror: Correspondence, 1950 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Mirror: Negotiations, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Mirror: Negotiations, 1939-1940 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Mirror: Negotiations, 1939-1941 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Mirror: Negotiations, 1939-1945 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Mirror: Negotiations, 1939-1945 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Mirror: Negotiations, 1940 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Mirror: Negotiations, 1941 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Mirror: Negotiations, 1942-1943 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Mirror: Negotiations, 1943 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Mirror: Negotiations, 1943-1944 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Mirror: Negotiations, 1943-1944 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Mirror: Negotiations, 1945 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - Mirror: Negotiations, 1946 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - Mirror: Negotiations, 1946 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - Mirror: Negotiations, 1946-1947 (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - Mirror: Negotiations, 1948-1950 (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - Mirror: Negotiations, 1949 (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - Mirror: Negotiations, 1950 (Box 46, Folder 33)
  - Mirror: Negotiations, 1950 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Mirror: Negotiations, 1950 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Mirror: Grievances (Labor Board), 1940-1941 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Mirror: Grievances, 1940-1941 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Mirror: Grievances (Schultz & Sullivan), 1942-1943 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Mirror: Grievances, 1943-1944 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Mirror: Grievances, 1943-1948 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Mirror: Grievances (War Labor Board), 1945 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Mirror: Grievances, 1948 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Mirror: Grievances, 1949-1950 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Mirror: Grievances, 1950 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Mirror: Shop Papers, 1935-1950 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Mirror: Shop Papers, 1940-1950 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Mirror: Contracts, 1946-1947 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Moody's Investor Service: Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Moody's Investor Service: Correspondence, 1940-1941 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Moody's Investor Service: Negotiations, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Moody's Investor Service: Shop Papers, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Morning Freiheit: Correspondence, 1940-1950 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Morning Freiheit: Negotiations, 1941 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Morning Freiheit: Negotiations, 1942-1943 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Morning Freiheit: Negotiations, 1943-1944 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Morning Freiheit: Negotiations, 1944-1945 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Morning Freiheit: Negotiations, 1944-1945 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Morning Freiheit: Negotiations, 1947-1950 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Morning Freiheit: Grievances, 1943-1944 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - Morning Freiheit: Contracts, 1940-1950 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Morning Telegraph: Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Morning Telegraph: Correspondence, 1942 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Morning Telegraph: Correspondence, 1942 (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - Morning Telegraph: Correspondence, 1942-1943 (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - Morning Telegraph: Correspondence, 1943 (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - Morning Telegraph: Correspondence, 1944-1950 (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - Morning Telegraph: Correspondence, 1945 (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - Morning Telegraph: Negotiations, 1942-1944 (Box 47, Folder 35)
  - Morning Telegraph: Negotiations, 1944-1945 (Box 47, Folder 36)
  - Morning Telegraph: Negotiations, 1944-1945 (Box 47, Folder 37)
  - Morning Telegraph: Negotiations, 1945-1946 (Box 47, Folder 38)
  - Morning Telegraph: Negotiations, 1947-1948 (Box 47, Folder 39)
  - Morning Telegraph: Negotiations, 1949-1950 (Box 47, Folder 40)
  - Morning Telegraph: Grievances, 1943-1944 (Box 47, Folder 41)
  - Morning Telegraph: Grievances, 1946 (Box 47, Folder 42)
  - Morning Telegraph: Grievances, 1947-1950 (Box 47, Folder 43)
  - Morning Telegraph: Leaflets, 1940-1950 (Box 47, Folder 44)
  - Morning Telegraph: Shop Papers, 1940-1950 (Box 47, Folder 45)
  - Morning Telegraph: Contracts, 1940-1950 (Box 47, Folder 46)
  - Nassau Daily Journal: Correspondence, 1939 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Nassau Daily Review Star: Correspondence, 1944-1945 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Nassau Daily Review Star: Correspondence, 1946 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Nassau Daily Review Star: Correspondence, 1947 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Nassau Daily Review Star: Shop Papers, 1935-1950 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Nassau Daily Review Star: Clippings, 1946 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - The Nation: Correspondence, 1940-1950 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - The Nation: Negotiations, 1939-1940 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - The Nation: Negotiations, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - The Nation: Negotiations, 1942-1943 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - The Nation: Negotiations, 1944-1945 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - The Nation: Negotiations, 1945 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - The Nation: Negotiations, 1946 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - The Nation: Negotiations, 1947 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - The Nation: Negotiations, 1948 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - The Nation: Negotiations, 1949-1950 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - The Nation: Grievances, 1948-1949 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - The Nation: Contracts, 1935-1950 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - The National Guardian: Correspondence I, 1950 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - The National Guardian: Correspondence II, 1950 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - The National Guardian: Negotiations I, 1949 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - The National Guardian: Negotiations II, 1949 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - The National Guardian: Negotiations, 1950 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - The National Herald: Negotiations (Greek), 1939-1940 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - The National Herald: Grievances (Greek), 1948 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - National Maritime Union: Negotiations I, 1946-1947 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - National Maritime Union: Negotiations II, 1946-1947 (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - National Maritime Union: Grievances, 1945-1947 (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - New Masses: Correspondence, 1941-1945 (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - New Masses: Negotiations, 1944-1947 (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - New Republic: Minutes, 1946-1947 (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - New Republic: Correspondence, 1946 (Box 48, Folder 32)
  - New Republic: Correspondence (Outside Activity), 1947 (Box 48, Folder 33)
  - New Republic: Correspondence, 1947-1950 (Box 48, Folder 34)
  - New Republic: Correspondence (Discharges), 1948 (Box 48, Folder 35)
  - New Republic: Correspondence (Investigating Committee), 1948 (Box 48, Folder 36)
  - New Republic: Negotiations, 1946 (Box 48, Folder 37)
  - New Republic: Negotiations, 1946-1947 (Box 48, Folder 38)
  - New Republic: Negotiations, 1948 (Box 48, Folder 39)
  - New Republic: Negotiations, 1949 (Box 48, Folder 40)
  - New Republic: Negotiations, 1949 (Box 48, Folder 41)
  - New Republic: Grievances, 1947-1949 (Box 48, Folder 42)
  - New Republic: Shop Papers, 1935-1950 (Box 48, Folder 43)
  - New York Age: Minutes, 1949 (Box 48, Folder 44)
  - New York Age: Correspondence, 1948-1949 (Box 48, Folder 45)
  - New York Age: Correspondence, 1950 (Box 48, Folder 46)
  - New York Age: Negotiations, 1949-1950 (Box 48, Folder 47)
  - New York Age: Grievances, 1949-1950 (Box 48, Folder 48)
  - New York Age: Shop Papers, 1935-1950 (Box 48, Folder 49)
  - New York Evening Journal: Correspondence, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 50)
  - New York Post: Minutes, 1940-1950 (Box 48, Folder 51)
  - New York Post: Bargaining, 1937-1947 (Box 48, Folder 51a)
  - New York Post: Correspondence, 1938 (Box 48, Folder 52)
  - New York Post: Correspondence, 1939 (Box 48, Folder 53)
  - New York Post: Correspondence, 1940 (Box 48, Folder 54)
  - New York Post: Correspondence, 1940-1941 (Box 48, Folder 55)
  - New York Post: Correspondence, 1942-1943 (Box 48, Folder 56)
  - New York Post: Correspondence, 1944 (Box 48, Folder 57)
  - New York Post: Correspondence, 1945 (Box 48, Folder 58)
  - New York Post: Correspondence (NWLB), 1945 (Box 48, Folder 59)
  - New York Post: Correspondence (Job Slotting), 1945-1949 (Box 48, Folder 60)
  - New York Post: Correspondence, 1946 (Box 48, Folder 61)
  - New York Post: Correspondence, 1947 (Box 48, Folder 62)
  - New York Post: Correspondence (Benefits), 1947 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - New York Post: Correspondence (Job), 1948 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - New York Post: Correspondence, 1948-1949 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - New York Post: Correspondence, 1948-1950 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - New York Post: Correspondence (Elections), 1950 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - New York Post: Negotiations, 1942-1943 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - New York Post: Negotiations, 1943 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - New York Post: Negotiations, 1943-1944 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - New York Post: Negotiations, 1944 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - New York Post: Negotiations, 1945 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - New York Post: Negotiations, 1947 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - New York Post: Negotiations, 1948 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - New York Post: Negotiations, 1948 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - New York Post: Negotiations, 1948 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - New York Post: Negotiations, 1948-1950 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - New York Post: Negotiations, 1949 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - New York Post: Negotiations, 1949-1950 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - New York Post: Grievances, 1939 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - New York Post: Grievances, 1940 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - New York Post: Grievances, 1941 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - New York Post: Grievances, 1946 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - New York Post: Grievances, 1947 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - New York Post: Grievances, 1948 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - New York Post: Grievances, 1948 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - New York Post: Grievances, 1948 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - New York Post: Grievances, 1949 (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - New York Post: Shop Papers, 1939-1950 (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - New York Post: Contracts, 1937-1950 (Box 49, Folder 28)
  - New York Star: Minutes, 1948 (Box 49, Folder 29)
  - New York Star: Negotiations, 1948 (Box 49, Folder 30)
  - New York Star: Shop Papers, 1948 (Box 49, Folder 31)
  - New York Sun: Correspondence, 1939-1940 (Box 49, Folder 32)
  - New York Sun: Correspondence, 1942-1945 (Box 49, Folder 33)
  - New York Sun: Correspondence, 1949 (Box 49, Folder 34)
  - New York Sun: Shop Papers, undated (Box 49, Folder 35)
  - New York Sun: Leaflets, 1942-1945 (Box 49, Folder 36)
  - New York Times: Minutes, 1938-1950 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - New York Times: Correspondence – Elections, 1938 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - New York Times: Correspondence – NLRB, 1937-1938 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - New York Times: Correspondence – Labor Board, 1939-1940 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - New York Times: Correspondence, 1939-1940 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - New York Times: Correspondence – Lawrence, 1940 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - New York Times: Correspondence, 1940-1941 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - New York Times: Correspondence, 1941 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - New York Times: Correspondence, 1941 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - New York Times: Correspondence, 1943-1944 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - New York Times: Correspondence – Maintenance of Membership, 1944 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - New York Times: Correspondence, 1944 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - New York Times: Correspondence, 1944-1945 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - New York Times: Correspondence, 1944-1946 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - New York Times: Correspondence, 1945 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - New York Times: Correspondence, 1945-1946 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - New York Times: Correspondence, 1946-1947 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - New York Times: Correspondence, 1947 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - New York Times: Correspondence, 1947 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - New York Times: Correspondence, 1948 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - New York Times: Correspondence, 1948 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - New York Times: Correspondence, 1948-1949 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - New York Times: Correspondence, 1948-1950 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - New York Times: Correspondence, 1949 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - New York Times: Correspondence, 1950 (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - New York Times: Correspondence - Resignation, 1950 (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - New York Times: Job Slotting, 1946 (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - New York Times: Negotiations, 1937-1940 (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - New York Times: Negotiations – Muras, Ken, 1938 (Box 50, Folder 29)
  - New York Times: Negotiations, 1939 (Box 50, Folder 30)
  - New York Times: Negotiations, 1940-1941 (Box 50, Folder 31)
  - New York Times: Negotiations, 1941 (Box 50, Folder 32)
  - New York Times: Negotiations, 1941 (Box 50, Folder 33)
  - New York Times: Negotiations, 1941 (Box 50, Folder 34)
  - New York Times: Negotiations, 1941 (Box 50, Folder 35)
  - New York Times: Negotiations, 1940-1941 (Box 50, Folder 36)
  - New York Times: Negotiations, 1941 (Box 50A, Folder 1)
  - New York Times: Negotiations, 1941 (Box 50A, Folder 2)
  - New York Times: Negotiations, 1941 (Box 50A, Folder 3)
  - New York Times: Negotiations, 1941 (Box 50A, Folder 4)
  - New York Times: Negotiations, 1941 (Box 50A, Folder 5)
  - New York Times: Negotiations, 1943 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - New York Times: Negotiations, 1943-1944 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - New York Times: Negotiations, 1943-1944 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - New York Times: Negotiations, 1944 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - New York Times: Negotiations, 1944-1945 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - New York Times: Negotiations, 1944-1945 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - New York Times: Negotiations, 1945-1946 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - New York Times: Negotiations, 1945-1946 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - New York Times: Negotiations, 1947 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - New York Times: Negotiations, 1947 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - New York Times: Negotiations, 1949 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - New York Times: Negotiations, 1950 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - New York Times: Grievances, 1940 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - New York Times: Grievances, 1940-1941 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - New York Times: Grievances, 1941 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - New York Times: Grievances, 1941 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - New York Times: Grievances, 1942 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - New York Times: Grievances, 1943 (Box 51, Folder 18)